{
    "problems": [
        {
            "question": "2+3+6-1",
            "answer": "10"
        },
        {
            "question": "2+3+6-1-3",
            "answer": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "2+3+6-1+10",
            "answer": "20"
        },
        {
            "question": "2+2",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "145+2+(14/2)-50",
            "answer": "104"
        },
        {
            "question": "300+200+100*2-(1000/2)",
            "answer": "200"
        },
        {
            "question": "234*4",
            "answer": "936"
        },
        {
            "question": "1000/2 + 500*2",
            "answer": "1500"
        },
        {
            "question": "51/4",
            "answer": "12.75"
        },
        {
            "question": "3+21 * 6 + (24-4) * 2",
            "answer": "169"
        }
    ]
}